magazineoutlet.com 2004-08-10

# Magazineoutlet.com

|  |   | 

**MagazineOutlet.com Privacy Statement**

****

MagazineOutlet.com presented by SynapseConnect, Inc., Synapse Solutions, Inc. and Gift Services, LLC, value your privacy and are dedicated to protecting your personal information. Our privacy statement is a summary of our privacy policy. You can read our complete privacy policy by clicking here. 

MagazineOutlet.com logs IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the site. We track your movement within the site, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. We use this information in aggregate and do not link it to you personally. We promise to take measures to protect all the personal information you provide at all times. We do not rent, sell or lease your personal information, and you may opt-out of the use of your information for secondary purposes at any time - click here for details. You also have the opportunity to correct or change the information you have provided to us. 

All of our programs are committed to provide you with: 

|  **Notice**  
---  
•  |  What personally identifiable information we collect   
•  |  How the information is used   
•  |  With whom the information may be shared   
  
**Consent**  
---  
•  |  What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of the information   
  
**Security**  
---  
•  |  Procedures we use to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the   
  |  information   
  
**Access**  
---  
•  |  How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information we have collected from   
  |  you   
  
To read our complete privacy policy, click here. 

SynapseConnect, Inc., Synapse Solutions, Inc. and Gift Services, LLC. provide various online programs. This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [MagazineOutlet.com](http://www.magazineoutlet.com/). 

**A Special Note About Children**

Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use any services on this site. 

**Order & Registration**

We request information from you on our order forms and when you register. This information is used for order fulfillment, billing, customer service, and to understand your areas of interest. You must provide delivery information and when applicable, your account number and type in order for us to fulfill your order. You may also be asked to supply a password that gives you access to your profile and order information. If you visit our programs by linking through one of our partners or affiliates, they may forward us your delivery and account information, saving you from reentering the information on our sites. 

**Tracking Technology**

If you have been offered our services through one of our marketing partners or affiliates (see "Use of Information" section below), we may share the information you enter with that partner or affiliate. To do so, we use a technology called clear GIFs, which automatically and securely transfer the information you enter. In the future, we may use other similar technologies on the site for the same purpose. If we do so, we will modify our privacy policy accordingly. See the "Notification of Changes" section below. 

**Network Advertising**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on other sites. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs (also known as action tags, single pixel GIFs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>. 

**Log Files**

We log IP addresses (a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet) in order to improve security, analyze trends and administer the site. We track your movement within the site, the pages from which you were referred, access times and browser types. We use this information in aggregate and do not link it to you personally. 

**Use of Information**

MagazineOutlet.com is brought to you by SynapseConnect, Inc., Synapse Solutions, Inc. and Gift Services, LLC. SynapseConnect collects and manages the data from these web sites. If your order includes merchandise, SynapseConnect gives your information to Gift Services, who processes that portion of your order. The information provided to Gift Services is not provided by Gift Services to any third party for marketing purposes. If your order includes software, SynapseConnect gives your information to Synapse Solutions, who processes that portion of your order. If your order includes magazines, SynapseConnect processes that portion of your order itself. 

_Synapse Group, Inc. Companies_

SynapseConnect, Inc. and Synapse Solutions, Inc. are wholly-owned subsidiaries of Synapse Group, Inc. From time to time, we may share your information with other subsidiaries of Synapse Group, Inc. in order to provide all the services necessary to fulfill your order as well as provide you with all of the opportunities Synapse Group has to offer. 

_Contractual Relationships_

We provide your information to our third party service vendors with whom we have contractual relationships for the purpose of servicing our processing of your order. These vendors provide various services on our behalf such as customer service, web hosting, billing and fulfillment. These vendors are not allowed to sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information and cannot use your information for any secondary purpose. 

_Third Party Marketing Affiliates and Publishers_

When you order a magazine, we forward your contact information to the applicable magazine publisher for fulfillment. If you visit any of our programs by linking through one of our partners or affiliates, your information also may be shared with the partner or affiliate which originated the link to our sites. In those instances, your information will be governed by the privacy policy of the magazine publishers for the titles you have chosen to receive, or said partners and affiliates. 

_Exceptional Circumstances_

Please note that if Gift Services, LLC, SynapseConnect, Inc., Synapse Solutions, Inc. or Synapse Group, Inc., or any of their lines of business are sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, the applicable customer database of one or all of these programs could be sold as part of that transaction. We also may have to release personally-identifying information when it is necessary to comply with judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders. 

**Links**

These web sites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that SynapseConnect, Synapse Solutions and Gift Services are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. When you leave our sites, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by these web sites. 

**Security**

These web sites take measures to protect your personal information by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, which is recognized as an industry standard in encryption technology. 

For our programs that require a credit card, we also offer our exclusive credit card guarantee. If your credit card number is ever used without your permission as a direct result of you having made a purchase on our web sites, we’ll reimburse you for the liability not covered by your credit card company, up to a maximum of $50. 

**Special Offers and Choice/Opt-Out**

From time to time, we may present you with specially selected offers from SynapseConnect or one of our partners. Out of respect for your privacy, you can forfeit these opportunities, by clicking here. 

**Site and Service Updates**

We communicate with you to provide requested services and on issues relating to your account. We also send site and subscription service updates. You are not able to unsubscribe from these important announcements, which contain important information about your order and the MagazineOutlet.com program. 

**Correcting/Updating Personal Information**

If you want to change your personal information (such as your address or account number) you can do so on each of our sites. Upon verification, we will provide you with the information we have for all your active orders placed with us. To request your record, click here. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our site by identifying them as changes to our previous privacy policy. We will identify those changes for at least 60 days so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Information Collection and Use**

SynapseConnect, Inc., Synapse Solutions, Inc. and Gift Services, LLC are the owners of the information collected on this site. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact the SynapseConnect Privacy Department as follows: 

  | SynapseConnect, Inc.  
---|---  
  | Attn: Privacy Department  
  | 5 High Ridge Park  
  | Stamford, CT 06905  
  | (203) 614-2518 (Phone)  
  | (203) 329-8217 (Fax)
